OSTAP FEDYSHYN

Personal

Phone number +447708820125

Email outao_eu@yahoo.com

Driving licence
B

Website https://outaos.pythonanywhere.com/home

LinkedInOstap Fedyshyn

Languages

Ukrainian
English
Russian
Chinese

Interests

 Hiking, nature, street art, web app development Public safety and emergency management analyst and sales manager with experience in marketing, data analysis, and business development. Conducted project on field assessments in China, Lebanon, Spain, Sierra Leone, Indonesia, and Brazil. Presented technical emergency management solutions before government officials and senior business leaders abroad. Currently, I am in the process of a career change, transitioning to work as a GIS professional.

Work experience

Overseas sales manager / Project analyst

Mar 2018 - Aug 2020

Beijing GSAFETY Technology Co., LTD., Beijing, China

- Improved and developed public safety and emergency management solutions.
- Conducted negotiations with foreign delegations, presented high-level and technical solutions and prepared agreement documentation.
- Analysed geospatial data.
- Implemented project assessments abroad and presented results and recommendations to senior management.
- Helped execute the following projects: disaster recovery, call & dispatch systems, mine pollution prevention, rainforest protection, smart firefighting and others.

Market analyst

Nov 2017 - Mar 2018

Beijing GSAFETY Technology Co., LTD., Beijing, China

- Researched, gathered, and analysed web analytics to identify potential projects abroad.
- Presented results to senior management.

Merchant

Mar 2014 - Aug 2015

Self-employed, Guangzhou, China

- Arranged shipments of goods from China to Ukraine.
- Conducted numerous successful negotiations with foreign traders in the Pearl River Delta Economic Zone.

Education and Qualifications

Geographical Information Science, MSc

Sep 2021 - Sep 2022

The University of Manchester, Manchester, UK

- Developed a full stack web application as my design dissertation using Python Flask framework and JavaScript.
- Conducted an extent analysis of Freetown's informal settlements using ArcGIS Pro.
- Worked as a student ambassador helping to promote the university with blog posts and videos.

Chinese Business and International Relations, MIB

Sep 2015 - Jul 2017

Beijing Foreign Studies University, Beijing, China

- Implemented a business development project in Foshan, Guangdong,
- Organized a "speed-dating", "Sittning" singing party and mountain trekking in Hebei's Taihang Mountains.

History, BA

Sep 2008 - Jun 2012

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv, Kyiv, Ukraine

- Participated in excavations of a medieval castle.
- Performed at university theatre.
- Organised mountain trekking in Carpathian and Crimean Mountains.

Skills

ArcGIS software

Microsoft Office package

QGIS software

Google Earth Engine

JavaScript

Python

SQL

R

Courses

Public Safety Summer SchoolTsinghua University, Beijing
Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

Globalization, Energy and SustainabilityJun 2016 - Jul 2016
Beijing Foreign Studies University

Geographic Information Systems (GIS) SpecialisationUC Davis, Coursera

Spatial Analysis. The New Frontier in AnalyticsMar 2021 - May 2021
Esri Training

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

Non-profit organisation

AIESEC Environmental Educator in Guangzhou, China (Jul 2013 - Dec 2013).

AIESEC Project Team Leader in Kyiv, Ukraine (Mar 2013 - May 2013).

UEFA EURO 2012 Volunteer (May 2012 - July 2012).